Victor Cojocaru

London Road 199A, RM7 9DJ **Mobile:** 07546367417 **Email:** cojocaruvictor05@gmail.com

Portfolio:

https://vc-tory.com/index.html

Personal Profile

My IT background started 5 years ago when I was graduated as Programming engineer at "Dunarea de Jos" University of Galati, Romania. My profile was based mostly on backend programming as C, Java, Python, database(SQL, MySQL), Android where to demonstrate the skills gained we had to do a project at the end of each course. From various reasons, I had to take a break for several years from programming and to work in positions with a different profile.

Because I'm an ambitious person, recently I decided to renew my IT knowledges and to do what I like. I was enrolled in a Digital Skills Bootcam at JustIT Training, where I have learned the fundamentals of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python and databases. I have now a portfolio with projects which showcase my skillset.

My next objective is to gain a role as a Junior Developer where I can contribute in the development of software solutions. Skills as rapid assimilation, result oriented, communication, analytical, teamwork, task organization may help me to be a suitable candidate.

Education and IT Training

September/2022 - Just IT Training Ltd, London

December/2022 Digital Skills Bootcamp: Software Development

A twelve week intensive bootcamp covering the fundamentals of

Web and Software development.

11/2021 - 12/2021 OpenEDG Python Institute, online

PCAP: Programming Essentials in Python

Core Modules: Universal concepts of computer programming, fundamental

programming techniques, standard language infrastructure, modules and packages, fundamentals of object-oriented

programming

Languages: Python

Certification: https://vc-tory.com/Documents/PCAP_certificate.pdf

01/2018-02/2018 Google Digital Garage

Digital Marketing

Core Modules: SEO, SEM, email marketing, social media marketing, Google

analytics

2013 - 2017 "Dunarea de Jos" University of Galati - Galati, Romania

Bachelor's in IT - Programming engineer

Languages: C, C++, OS, SQL, MySQL, Java, JavaScript, Computer Networks,

Python, Android, IA

2010 - 2013 "Mircea Eliade" school, Nisporeni, Republic of Moldova

Diploma: A-Level in Exact Sciences

Software Development Skills: Python, MySQL(SQLite), MongoDB

Web Technology: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, API

Core Programming Languages: Python, MySQL, JavaScript

Projects:

- Portfolio A web-hosted portfolio displaying my coding skills developed at JustIT Bootcamp.
- **Cryptocurrency prices** Webpage of top 10 cryptocurrencies with API for up to date Data, where we can search for details about specified cryptocurrency.
- Database

Employment History

01/2022-07/2022 SDS - Southern Ductwork Services, London Duct Fitters Improver

- Installed new duct systems and related accessories according to company, safety manufacturer specifications.
- Ensured complete protection of customers property during installation/service of product.
- Provided prompt, efficient service and proactive communication with customers.
- Maintained highest level of standards for time management and quality completions.
- Maintained highest level of customer service while performing installations.

01/2021-01/2022 SDS - Southern Ductwork Services, London Duct Fitters Mate

- Ensured that tools and safety equipment are kept in good condition
- Ensured that the company vehicle is equipped with sufficient tools, materials and fixings at all times.
- Assisted with fitting/mounting the duct gathers and ancillaries in line with manufacturers installation specifications.
- Prepared the materials(duct, fans, silencer, unistrut) with everything needed to be ready for fitting.

01/2019-11/2020 PPHE Support Services Ltd, London Linen Porter

- As linen porter, I was responsible to help the room attendant with all necessary to clean up the room in time and at the top quality.
- Ensured that the linen and uniforms are neatly and systematically arranged and stacked.
- Responsible to manage the guest requests in timely and efficient manners.
- Received, sorted and double checked conditions of all linen and towels, records all outgoing
 and incoming from the laundry thoroughly before storing and issuing.
- Performed all duties and responsibilities in a timely and efficient manner in accordance with established company policies and procedures to achieve overall objectives of this position.
- Assisted other departments wherever necessary and maintained good working relationships

01/2018-11/2018 Mar-Ina Prodprest, Galati - Romania IT Engineer

- Installed and configured computer hardware, software, networks and applications.
- I continuously monitored and maintained the systems and networks.
- Kept a record of issues, along with solutions, to refer back to in future instances. Kept a record of issues, along with solutions, to refer back to in future instances

•

 Responded to technical support calls from other staff members and communicate how to resolve issues.

Interests and Achievements

Computing: Good Knowledge of MS Office, Windows Installation, Solving pc issues(errors, viruses,...) – especially friends/family ones, Installation of PC Applications, setting up PC/Internet, etc.

Hobbies:

- One of my favourite hobbies is the sport(because I like challenges), especially running and tennis, which I am doing weekly. Other sport preferences are football, swimming when I have time for them.
- I like to study the universe and to know as much as I can about our world, from where we come, what is the beginning of everything, how stars, planets, galaxies are formed... In the future I wish to travel in space.
- Crypto investments one of my recent discoveries.
- Books especially personal development books. My favourite one is "Secrets of Success" by *Dale Carnegie*, the best book I've read.
- Logical games as Sudoku, Puzzle, chess,...
- For rest of my time: music, movies, gaming, technology,...
- At the end, I like to spend my holidays travelling into new places, to see new cultures, to discover new cities.

Additional Info: Driving Licence

References available upon request